This School Rocks!
School of Life is a comedy, drama, family film directed by William Dear.
At Fallbrook Middle School, the annual
student-elected Teacher of the Year award is held.
And every year for the last 43 years Norman Warner or most fondly
called Stormin' Norman Warner has won the award.
Now that he has died, the burden of carrying the legacy falls into the hands of Matt Warner, the
son of the late Norman Warner who has always lived in the shadow of his father.
Matt Warner, played by David Paymer.
Mr. D, played by Ryan Reynolds.
Elli Warner, played by Kate Vernon.
Dylan Warner, played by Andrew Robb.
Norman Warner, played by John Astin.
Principal Bass, played by Don MacKay.
School of Life is a 2005 made-for-television comedy-drama film starring Ryan Reynolds
about a teacher who moves to a town and shakes the old school ways up a bit.
The film premiered on ABC Family on February 19, 2005.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.